# **SALLY MOHAMED**

I'm Sally Mohamed, a **Back-End developer** with 5 years of experience. I'm a specialist in managing and develop application and websites with experience in multiple programming languages and database. I deliver and maintain well-designed, high quality working software.

### **CONTACT**

- +201015987079
- engsallycis@gmail.com
- Giza, Egypt
- in linkedin.com/in/sally-mohamed-23708769

## **SKILL**

PHP

Javascript

MySQL

OPP

Design Pattern

HTML

CSS

MVC (Codeigniter FRAMEWORK)

Digital marketing

#### **EDUCATION**

2007 - 2011

**Mansoura University** 

- Bachelor of Computer Science
- It department
- General Grade: Very Good

#### **INTERESTS**

programing, computer science, reading

### **LANGUAGES**

Arabic(Native)

English(Fluent)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

April 2018 - till now online PHP trainer and online developer, from home

July 2016 - March 2018

**Vullet Web Company**, Giza

Senior PHP developer

 PHP, Codelgnitor, MySql ,Aptana,Wampserver,GIT

**July 2013 - December 2013** 

MHLOL Web Company, Giza

Senior PHP developer

 PHP, CodeIgnitor, MySql ,Aptana,Wampserver

November 2012 - MAY 2013 IMZ Web Company, Mansoura

Senior PHP developer

 PHP, Codelgnitor, MySql ,GIT,Aptana,Wampserver

May 2012 - October 2012

Allamwahd company, Mansoura

PHP developer

PHP developer

• PHP, Codelgnitor, MySql, GIT

January 2010 - February 2010

Elsa3a Company, Mansoura

• PHP, dream waver, MySQL

## **PROJECTS**

http://alamwahd.com/ar/plzwazfny

http://alamwahd.com/ar/l3abe

http://alamwahd.com/ar/cinema4us

http://alamwahd.com/ar/livetv4us

http://www.alamwahdit.com/kids

http://www.reservationgate.com

http://www.mtm-autoparts.com/

http://www.privatetoursinegypt.com/

http://eg-ata.com/

http://www.belisted.org/

http://elzamek.com/

#### **AWARDS**

Our graduation project has won the third position in ESEA 2011

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Interactive and fast enough to learn new technologies and sciences.
- Advanced Research Abilities.
- Highly Communications Skills.
- Self Motivated.
- Hard worker.
- Ambitious.
- Ability to work in a group or individually according to the job requirements.

## **CERTIFICATES**

- 1. CCNA track 1 FROM CISCO ACADEMIC.
- 2. PHP Project CERIFICATION FROM ITIDA and

UTC

- 3. ITesstintial1 from ITEC COMPANY.
- 4. Java Standard Edition in GROUN Company
- 5. DEVELOPER AND BUSSINESS WITH ASP.NET

WORKSHOP FROM ITEC COMPANY.

6. PHP DEVELOP AND PROGRAMMING FROM

GT4 COMPANY.

- 7. ICDL FROM MANSOURA UNIVERSITY.
- 8. Attending seminar in Network AT ITC CENTER.
- 9. Attending seminar in Graphic "AutoCAD & 3dmax
- " AT ITC CENTER
- 10. IT Business and Development from ITEC

**COMPANY** 

11. Digital marketing courses from Udacity